{
    "id": "c82be77a58444a439445c8ba21ba9d49",
    "title": "Subject Verb Agreement",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Man and woman ………………… complementary to each other.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "32f4be9efee8431bbddd1404606bf217"
        },
        {
            "question": "Plenty of mangoes and bananas ………………… available in this season.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d4c892cdf702424c98f9912a4ef05220"
        },
        {
            "question": "A dictionary and an atlas …………………… missing from the library.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7c34bf9fa32f4326b0a7967233071525"
        },
        {
            "question": "The leader as well as his brothers ………………… to the same tribe.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "belong",
                "belongs"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "81c3490c1090411fa3d2ee961cff44df"
        },
        {
            "question": "Cats and dogs ……………….…….. not get along.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "does"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1d29deced888492baa84b1f48834288d"
        },
        {
            "question": "The brothers as well as their sister …………………… .. good at their studies.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a7b3960c66794058910e48e808ee9822"
        },
        {
            "question": "The students accompanied by their teacher …………………. gone on a picnic.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "have"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "51050d9bea574fb38880753269b5525b"
        },
        {
            "question": "A lot of houses ………………… collapsed in the storm.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "have"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "82ecf8a8fb864624917241ab5809490f"
        },
        {
            "question": "The children as well as their mother …………………. missing.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "36aa9194132845b0a1e820abaae4981e"
        },
        {
            "question": "A large sum of money ………………… stolen.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0108cd1a9d3b43adab9ec0643c15c6e7"
        }
    ]
}